turbotrafficsystem.com 2011-12-31

# Privacy Policy | Turbo Traffic System

Browse >

[Home](http://www.turbotrafficsystem.com/members "Browse to: Home") / Privacy Policy 

**PRIVACY POLICY**  
Welcome to  **Turbo Traffic System** (the “Site”).

We understand that privacy online is important to users of our Site, especially when conducting business. This statement governs our privacy policies with respect to those users of the Site (“Visitors”) who visit without transacting business and Visitors who register to transact business on the Site and make use of the various services offered by **Turbo Traffic System** (collectively, “Services”) (“Authorized Customers”).

**“Personally Identifiable Information”**  
refers to any information that identifies or can be used to identify, contact, or locate the person to whom such information pertains, including, but not limited to, name, address, phone number, fax number, email address, financial profiles, social security number, and credit card information. Personally Identifiable Information does not include information that is collected anonymously (that is, without identification of the individual user)  
or demographic information not connected to an identified individual.

**What Personally Identifiable Information is collected?**  
We may collect basic user profile information from all of our Visitors. We collect the following additional information from our Authorized Customers: the names, addresses, phone numbers and email addresses of Authorized Customers, the nature and size of the business, and the nature and size of the advertising inventory that the Authorized Customer intends to purchase or sell.

**What organizations are collecting the information?**  
In addition to our direct collection of information, our third party service vendors (such as credit card companies, clearinghouses and banks) who may provide such services as credit, insurance, and escrow services may collect this information from our Visitors and Authorized Customers. We do not control how these third parties use such information, but we do ask them to disclose how they use personal information provided to them from Visitors and Authorized Customers. Some of these third parties may be intermediaries that act solely as links in the distribution chain, and do not store, retain, or use the information given to them.

**How does the Site use Personally Identifiable Information?**  
We use Personally Identifiable Information to customize the Site, to make appropriate service offerings, and to fulfill buying and selling requests on the Site. We may email Visitors and Authorized Customers about research or purchase and selling opportunities on the Site or information related to the subject matter of the Site. We may also use Personally Identifiable Information to contact Visitors and Authorized Customers in response to specific inquiries, or to provide requested information.  [](http://www.weblawgenerator.com/)While actual use of any Personal Information may be quite conservative, it may be used for general solicitation by this Website or other entities it is sold to, rented or shared with.

**With whom may the information may be shared?**  
Personally Identifiable Information about Authorized Customers may be shared with other Authorized Customers who wish to evaluate potential transactions with other Authorized Customers. We may share aggregated information about our Visitors, including the demographics of our Visitors and Authorized Customers, with our affiliated agencies and third party vendors. We also offer the opportunity to “opt out” of receiving information or being contacted by us or by any agency acting on our behalf.

**How is Personally Identifiable Information stored?**  
Personally Identifiable Information collected by **Turbo Traffic System** is securely stored and is not accessible to third parties or employees of **Turbo Traffic System** except for use as indicated above. 

**What choices are available to Visitors regarding collection, use and distribution of the information?**  
Visitors and Authorized Customers may opt out of receiving unsolicited information from or being contacted by us and/or our vendors and affiliated agencies by responding to emails as instructed, or by contacting us

**Are Cookies Used on the Site?**  
Cookies are used for a variety of reasons. We use Cookies to obtain information about the preferences of our Visitors and the services they select. We also use Cookies for security purposes to protect our Authorized Customers. For example, if an Authorized Customer is logged on and the site is unused for more than 10 minutes, we will automatically log the Authorized Customer off.

**How does Google Traffic System   use login information?  
****Turbo Traffic System** uses login information, including, but not limited to, IP addresses, ISPs, and browser types, to analyze trends, administer the Site, track a user’s movement and use, and gather broad demographic information.

**What partners or service providers have access to Personally Identifiable Information from Visitors and/or Authorized Customers on the Site?**  
**Turbo Traffic System** has entered into and will continue to enter into partnerships and other affiliations with a number of vendors.  
Such vendors may have access to certain Personally Identifiable Information on a need to know basis for evaluating Authorized Customers for service eligibility.  
Our privacy policy does not cover their collection or use of this information.  
Disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information to comply with law. We will disclose Personally Identifiable Information in order to comply with a court order or subpoena or a request from a law enforcement agency to release information. We will also disclose Personally Identifiable Information when reasonably necessary to protect the safety of our Visitors and Authorized Customers.

**How does the Site keep Personally Identifiable Information secure?**  
All of our employees are familiar with our security policy and practices. The Personally Identifiable Information of our Visitors and Authorized Customers is only accessible to a limited number of qualified employees who are given a password in order to gain access to the information. We audit our security systems and processes on a regular basis. Sensitive information, such as credit card numbers or social security numbers, is protected by encryption protocols, in place to protect information sent over the Internet. While we take commercially reasonable measures to maintain a secure site, electronic communications and databases are subject to errors, tampering and break-ins, and we cannot guarantee or warrant that such events will not take place and we will not be liable to Visitors or Authorized Customers for any such occurrences.

**How can Visitors correct any inaccuracies in Personally Identifiable Information?**  
Visitors and Authorized Customers may contact us to update Personally Identifiable Information about them or to correct any inaccuracies by emailing us

**Can a Visitor delete or deactivate Personally Identifiable Information collected by the Site?**  
We provide Visitors and Authorized Customers with a mechanism to delete/deactivate Personally Identifiable Information from the Site’s database by contacting contact us. However, because of backups and records of deletions, it may be impossible to delete a Visitor’s entry without retaining some residual information. An individual who requests to have Personally Identifiable Information deactivated will have this information functionally deleted, and we will not sell, transfer, or use Personally Identifiable Information relating to that individual in any way moving forward.

**What happens if the Privacy Policy Changes?**  
We will let our Visitors and Authorized Customers know about changes to our privacy policy by posting such changes on the Site. However, if we are changing our privacy policy in a manner that might cause disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information that a Visitor or Authorized Customer has previously requested not be disclosed, we will contact such Visitor or Authorized Customer to allow such Visitor or Authorized Customer to prevent such disclosure.

**Links:**  
This web site contains links to other web sites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are moving to another web site. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their privacy policies may differ from ours.

**Spam:**  
By providing information to this Website that forms the basis of communication from you, such as an email address, you waive all rights to file complaints concerning unsolicited email or spam from this Website since, by providing such information, you agree to receive communication from the Company or other marketing organizations. However, all email communication with you shall contain an ‘unsubscribe’ link where you may notify the Website that you no longer wish to receive solicitations or information from the Website and your name will be removed from the general solicitation database.

**Commitment to Data Security  
**This Website takes measures to protect its data that contains information related to you. However, no security system is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee the security of our database, nor can we guarantee that information will not be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the Internet. As a consideration for viewing this Website, you waive any and all claims for damages of any nature against the Company and you further acknowledge that the Company is not responsible for damages to you arising from any misuse of your Personal Information.

**Age restrictions:**  
By using this site, you agree that you are over 18 years of age.

**Disputes:**  
In the event of any dispute, claim or controversy (collectively “Dispute”) between you and the Company, including but not limited to Disputes arising from: use of this Website; the Privacy Policy herein; the Terms of Use herein, any purchases made in connection with this Website; or any other claims whether in contract, tort or otherwise; you hereby consent and agree that such Dispute shall be settled by binding arbitration by the American Arbitration Association in accordance with the Arbitration Rules then in effect. The hearing shall be conducted in the City of Boise, Idaho. The decision of the arbitrator shall be final and binding upon all parties and any award of the arbitrator(s) may be entered as a judgment in any court of competent jurisdiction.

The prevailing party shall be awarded all of the filing fees and related administrative costs. Administrative and other costs of enforcing an arbitration award, including the costs of subpoenas, depositions, transcripts and the like, witness fees, payment of reasonable attorney’s fees, and similar costs related to collecting an arbitrator’s award, will be added to, and become a part of, the amount due pursuant to this provision. Any questions involving contract interpretation shall use the laws of Idaho

**Questions, Comments or Reports of Incidents**  
You may direct questions, comments or reports to: [legal@turbotrafficsystem.com](mailto:legal@turbotrafficsystem.com)
